<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on /</title><link>https://beau.so/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on /</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 00:48:54 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://beau.so/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Allowing Matrix (synapse) federation without exposing 8448 via /.well-known/ delegation and nginx</title><link>https://beau.so/posts/well-known-matrix-synapse/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 00:48:54 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://beau.so/posts/well-known-matrix-synapse/</guid><description>problem I have a matrix server called example.com, but it&amp;rsquo;s actually hosted on matrix.example.com. I want to keep the cosmetic name of example.com and have all federation traffic route through 443 instead of 8488.
what is delegation? Delegation is just a fancy term in the Matrix world for having a Matrix server name of example.com while having the actual endpoint other servers connect to being different, for example:
different.example.com:443 There are two main reasons why this is useful:</description></item><item><title>Clean YAML DNS management with TF and Cloudflare</title><link>https://beau.so/posts/dns_with_tf_cf/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 17:06:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://beau.so/posts/dns_with_tf_cf/</guid><description>Intro - Avoiding bad patterns There are two uninspiring patterns I&amp;rsquo;ve observed with DNS management via Terraform (be it R53, Cloudflare etc):
Resource blocks for each individual record.
This is fine if you know you&amp;rsquo;re only really going to have a few records, but it almost always ends up being a short sighted approach (especially with multiple domains), repeating attribute after attribute e.g.: 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 resource &amp;#34;aws_route53_record&amp;#34; &amp;#34;example_cname&amp;#34; { .</description></item><item><title>Init</title><link>https://beau.so/posts/init/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 08:52:46 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://beau.so/posts/init/</guid><description>This blog is generated using hugo, a static site generator framework. It allows me to keep the source DRY by using Golang html/template syntax and not worry about any dependencies or additional overhead.</description></item></channel></rss>